

ABOUT ME

I'm an impact-driven product designer with around three years of professional experience in the tech industry. My passion lies in crafting meaningful and impactful digital products. I also strive to help brands improve their digital experiences that address user needs and business goals.

TECH SKILLS

DESIGN DEVELOPMENT TOOLS TOOLS

Figma HTML/CSS
Sketch Javascript/jQuery
Adobe CC Google Analytics
Principle Wordpress
Overflow Git/GitHub
Miro Zeplin

COMPETENCIES

Visual Design Wireframing
Experience Design Prototyping
Interaction Design Info Architecture
Interface Design User Research
Product Strategy User Testing

EDUCATION

SIMON FRASER UNIVERSITY

B/A - Interactive Arts + Technology Design Concentration

Graduated with Distinction and Co-op Education Award 2014 - 2019

ACHIEVEMENTS

DEAN'S HONOR ROLL FALL 2014

Awarded to students for achieving a 3.50 (out of 4.33) or higher GPA.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

UX/UI Designer / Zaui Software

DEC 2019 - APR 2020

- Collaborated with developers and product experts to design flows and features for Zaui's new web booking engine and back-office platform.
- Created wireframes, high-fidelity mockups, and interactive prototypes for the new web booking engine and back-office platform.
- Communicated design intentions and interactions in Agile environment.

Digital Designer / PayByPhone

OCT 2018 - APR 2019

- Redefined the user experience and designed the interface of the new parking operators (B2B) and careers pages.
- Produced marketing materials for print and digital such as promotional banners, posters, postcards, display ads, and social media graphics.
- Consulted with various stakeholders for multiple design projects and tasks.

UX/UI Designer / BSTRO

MAY - SEP 2018

- Collaborated with senior designers and developers in designing digital experiences for Johnson δ Johnson, Chef Software, The San Francisco Marathon, and two other startup clients.
- Day-to-day included creative concepting, competitive analysis, sitemap drafting, wireframing, mockups design, and prototyping.
- Contributed to internal design projects and marketing initiatives through social media, email marketing campaign, and blog post.

UX/UI Designer / Buzzlt Inc.

SEP 2017 - AUG 2018

- Worked collaboratively with a product manager and a developer in redesigning Buzzlt's website and mobile apps in a startup environment.
- Led the design process from conducting user research, user testing, wireframing, mockups design, user flows, and developing brand guidelines.
- Overhauled the visual design and user experience of the entire Android δ iOS app by producing 5O+ sets of end to end mockups.

UX/UI Designer / GenomeMe

JAN - JUN 2017

- Completed the development of GenomeMe's major web redesign project.
- Designed layouts, streamlined flows, icons, and interactions for over 20+ responsive web pages and developed them using Foundation framework.